=The Little Red Matchmaker= =Episode 13=
=الخاطبة الحمراء الصغيرة= =الحلقة 13=
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
This is
هذا هو
a woman's hair.
شعر المرأة.
Other women's hairs can be used for curses.
ويمكن استخدام شعر النساء الأخريات للشتائم.
Can your hairs
يمكن شعرك
suppress curses?
قمع اللعنات؟
With this sachet,
مع هذا الكيس،
you will no longer fear women.
لن تخاف النساء بعد الآن.
You look good when smiling.
تبدو جيدًا عندما تبتسم.
You should deliver the medicine.
يجب عليك تسليم الدواء.
(Great Doctor with Utmost Sincerity)
(دكتور عظيم وفي قمة الإخلاص)
Master, what are you doing?
سيد، ماذا تفعل؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Ah.
آه.
Hey.
يا.
Master, what are you doing?
سيد، ماذا تفعل؟
Ah.
آه.
Eh.
إيه.
Yingying.
ينغينغ.
Do you feel that Master has been acting strange?
هل تشعر أن السيد كان يتصرف بغرابة؟
Speaking of which,
بالحديث عن هذا الموضوع،
indeed, he has been.
لقد كان بالفعل.
Yeah.
نعم.
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
He must be feeling lonely after losing Miss Siyue.
لا بد أنه يشعر بالوحدة بعد خسارة الآنسة Siyue.
Oh.
أوه.
Daniu.
دانيو.
We should help him out.
يجب أن نساعده.
Definitely.
قطعاً.
Hmm.
همم.
Why do you keep following me?
لماذا تستمرين بمتابعتي؟
Master.
يتقن.
Have you been sleeping poorly?
هل كنت تنام بشكل سيئ؟
So you feel down.
لذلك تشعر بالإحباط.
Also,
أيضًا،
you feel anxious
تشعر بالقلق
and pressured.
والضغط.
There are many things you can't say.
هناك أشياء كثيرة لا يمكنك قولها.
(Could she have found out?)
(هل كان من الممكن أن تكتشف ذلك؟)
(Did I make it too obvious?)
(هل جعلت الأمر واضحًا جدًا؟)
What are you thinking?
بماذا تفكر؟
Do your work.
قم بعملك.
Why has he been running hot and cold?
لماذا كان يركض ساخنًا وباردًا؟
Turns out that when one falls for someone,
اتضح أنه عندما يقع شخص ما في حب شخص ما،
one will be the loneliest.
سيكون المرء الأكثر وحدة.
Master.
يتقن.
Dress up well tomorrow.
اللباس جيدا غدا.
I'll take you for treatment.
سآخذك للعلاج.
Take me for treatment?
تأخذني للعلاج؟
What illness do I have?
ما هو المرض الذي أعاني منه؟
Loneliness.
الشعور بالوحدة.
Is she asking me out
هل تطلب مني الخروج
for a date?
لموعد؟
Unexpectedly,
بشكل غير متوقع،
Tian Xi and Hong Luan are still tough without magical powers.
لا يزال Tian Xi وHong Luan قويين بدون قوى سحرية.
The deeper the bond between them, the harder it is to deal with.
فكلما كانت العلاقة بينهما أعمق، أصبح التعامل معها أصعب.
Your magical power hasn't recovered yet.
قوتك السحرية لم تتعاف بعد
We must find another way.
يجب أن نجد طريقة أخرى.
I'll break them up.
سوف أقوم بتفريقهم.
I'll arrange a wrong marriage for Jiang Changqing.
سأرتب زواجًا خاطئًا لـ Jiang Changqing.
Hmph.
همف.
Muke.
نحن.
Stop thinking about the poor Mr. Zhang.
توقف عن التفكير في السيد تشانغ الفقير.
I've found good men in the city for you.
لقد وجدت رجالاً صالحين في المدينة من أجلك.
Choose one.
اختر واحدة.
Miss Muke, my family is the richest in the east city.
آنسة موك، عائلتي هي الأغنى في المدينة الشرقية.
My father is a high-ranking official.
والدي مسؤول رفيع المستوى.
Come on.
تعال.
The best way to mess up a relationship is
أفضل طريقة لإفساد العلاقة هي
to start a new one.
لبدء واحدة جديدة.
(To be continued)
(يتبع)
In the future,
فى المستقبل،
I will never
لن أفعل أبدا
make your heart
اصنع قلبك
or hands cold.
أو برودة اليدين.
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪ مع اقتراب الليل المقمر ♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪ أوزة برية منفردة تطير في الضباب ♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪ القمر المتضائل عميق في التفكير ♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪ إلقاء ضوء ذهبي على الطريق ♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪ أنا مشتاق للعودة إلى المنزل ♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪ لقد تخليت عن الزراعة من أجل حياة جديدة ♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪ وللجمال الذي في قلبي ♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪نلتقي فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪تتشابك الأرواح مع مرور الوقت♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪ المصير المحطم يكسر الرابطة ♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪ وأقضي بقية حياتي معك ♪